installmac.com 2017-02-05

# Privacy Policy | InstallMac

**End-user Privacy Policy**

Last modified on April 8, 2013.

This Privacy Policy is designed to help You decide whether to use InstallMac and in what manner. This Policy is incorporated into, subject to and a part of InstallMac’s Terms of Service.

During your use of the InstallMac delivery and installation platform (“InstallMac”) for the purpose of installing the Software, InstallMac gathers information from your computer. Genieo understands You wish to keep your information private, and that You value our emphasis on keeping your information safe and discrete. As a result we have drafted the following privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to inform You of the ways in which we gather and use information relating to You and your use of InstallMac.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MAY NOT AND SHOULD NOT USE INSTALLMAC.

The definitions in the Terms of Service apply to this Policy unless stated otherwise.

**Scope of This Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Policy governs your use of InstallMac alone and does not apply to third party services, as well as to third party services incorporated into InstallMac. This Policy does not relate to any use, storing or gathering of information by the Software, The Approved Offers and/or the advertisements that may be presented to You during and after the installation process.

For information regarding the manner in which said third party software uses your personal information, please refer to their respective privacy policies as they are not provided by InstallMac.

**Technical Information**

Upon authorizing the installation process, InstallMac retrieves technical information from your computer such as (without limitation) the type and version of your computer’s operating system, IE browser version and installed hardware, Java resource availability, .NET resources availability and your C-Class IP address (the “Technical Information”).

This Technical Information is used by our servers to provide, maintain and improve the InstallMac operation and services, such as (without limitation) by verifying that the installed Software and Additional Software are compatible with your computer ; by determining which Additional Software and of what version should be offered to You and installed on your computer; by correlating errors with certain Technical Information for debugging purposes; and by creating and managing statistics to guide future improvements and developments.

In addition, the Technical Information is used for Fraud Detection.

The Technical Information is stored on our servers.

**Personal Information**

We may collect personal information, such as country/region (the “Personal Information”).

This Personal Information is used by our servers in order to improve InstallMac operation and services and to present You with Offers which are better suited for You.

The Personal Information is stored on our servers.

**Installation Information**

In addition we may gather information regarding the installation process, including with regard to the Offers presented to You via InstallMac, The Approved Offers installed on your computer and Technical Information regarding the installation process, such as, without limitation, success/failure, duration, malfunctions, errors, etc. (the “Installation Information”).

The Installation Information is used to provide, maintain and improve InstallMac’s operation and services.

The Installation Information is shared, in an aggregated form and without any personally identifiable information, with our affiliates for billing and statistical reporting purposes with respect of InstallMac performance in installing their software (i.e. Software and/or Approved Offers).

**Cookies**

We may use cookies (or equivalents, such as flash cookies or pixels) to correlate between your computer and information stored in our servers. Any information derived from cookie use, shall be treated as Technical Information or Personal Information, as described herein, based on the type of information.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties, when this is required in order to provide, maintain or improve the InstallMac operation and services.

We may NOT share personally identifiable information with any third party, except in an aggregated and/or statistical form.

We may share your Personal Information and other information in special cases if we have a good reason to belief that it is necessary to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, violation of our policies or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between You and Genieo, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Genieo, its partners, its affiliates, users and/or the public.

**No Obligation to Store Information**

Nothing in this Policy is interpreted as an obligation to store information, and we may, at our own discretion, delete or avoid from recording and storing any and all information.

**Children Protection**

Regardless of the aforementioned, we do not knowingly collect or store information regarding children under the age of 13.

**Information Warranty Disclaimer**

Notwithstanding anything else in this Policy, we are not responsible for the accuracy, correctness and security of any of the information we gather, store and disclose to You or to anyone else.

**Review and Deletion**

We value your privacy and control over your personal information, and therefore You may, at any time, notify us that You wish to either review your personal information or delete it. You can notify us by sending an email to our legal department at info@InstallMac.com. In order to delete or allow You to review your personal information, we may require that You provide us with identifying information or install additional software to allow such review.

Inquiry Should You feel that your privacy was invaded or your personal information reached third parties without your authorization, You should contact us immediately in order to allow our legal department to commence an investigation. In such case, You may be required to provide us with additional information in order to allow such inquiry.

**Data Security**

We place great emphasis on the security and integrity of your information and the data stored in our systems.

InstallMac is provided under the best commercially reasonable data security practices, in order to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or deletion of any and all information stored in our systems.

You acknowledge, however, that no such effort can completely guarantee the security of the stored data, that breaches of security are still a possibility both regarding our systems and that a data security breach resulting in unauthorized access to your information can occur in third party system (for example, ISP’s and hosting services providers).

As a result, we do NOT warrant or ensure the integrity and security of the data stored in our systems, including without limitation your information.

We shall notify any user whose information is suspected of being accessed, disclosed, altered or deleted by an unauthorized person, so that he can take appropriate measure to minimize the adverse effect of such a data security breach (Breach Notification). Such Breach Notification will be given in a reasonable time after we learn of said breach, unless we deem, at our sole discretion, that such Notification might hinder and prevent ongoing efforts to detect the source of the breach.

For the avoidance of doubt, a Breach Notification does NOT constitute an admission by us that the breach occurred as a result of malpractice, failure, bad faith or negligence on our behalf or that the breach even occurred in our systems.

**Change of Ownership**

In the event of a change of ownership or control of all or part of Genieo, including without limitation through acquisition, merger or sale, we reserve the right to sell all or part of the personal information we store in our systems.

You acknowledge that in the event of bankruptcy, insolvency or receivership, we may have no control over the use and transfer of your personal information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Policy may be revised from time to time at our sole discretion. The last revision will be reflected in the “Last modified by” heading above.
